Hey there. I'm Miriam and I work on student motivation and learning science at Udacity.
嘿那里 我是米里亚姆 我在 Udacity 的学习动机和学习科学方面工作
I'll pop up at different moments throughout your needed degree experience,
我会在你需要的学位经历的不同时刻
to give you context for why we've designed your learning experience as we have.
为您提供背景 说明为什么我们设计了您的学习体验
The goal of the entire Eudacity team is to support you in meeting your goals,
整个 Eudacity 团队的目标是支持您实现目标
whether you're here to expand your understanding of topics you're interested in,
你是来扩大你对你感兴趣的话题的了解吗
or unlock a whole new stage of your career.
或者开启你职业生涯的全新阶段
To help you grow in the ways that you want to,
以你想要的方式帮助你成长
we're going to provide you with productive challenges that will stretch your brain,
我们将向你提供富有成效的挑战
as well as powerful support from your community.
以及您所在社区的强大支持
We'll guide you in learning by doing, through your projects,
我们会引导你学习通过你的项目
through helping out your fellow students,
帮助你的同学
and through questions we asked you in the classroom to
通过我们在教室里问你的问题
let you play around with your new knowledge and skills.
让你发挥你的新知识和技能
Actively engaging your brain in these ways will help you
以这些方式积极参与你的大脑会帮助你
develop deep, flexible, long-lasting learning.
发展深度 灵活 持久的学习
We can't wait to see where you go and what you do with all that you gain here.
我们迫不及待地想看看你去的地方和你在这里收获的一切